<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:magento:module:MageSuite_Changelog:etc/changelog.xsd">
    <module id="MageSuite_Wishlist" name="MageSuite_Wishlist">
        <changelog>
            <tag version="1.0.0" date="2022-07-15">
                <entry>
                    <type>INIT</type>
                    <overview>Initial release</overview>
                    <description>
                        Extend wishlist in customerData, add product ids for all items from wishlist.
                        Add selected class for towishlist element for all product tiles and wishlist icons on PDP that are on wishlist.
                        Move tile ajax add-to-wishlist functionality from magesuite-priduct-tile-module.
                        Add ajax add to wishlist functionality for PDP wishlist icon.
                    </description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="1.0.1" date="2022-07-21">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add wishlist script to cms and cart pages. Handle the scenario when icon is missing</overview>
                    <description>
                        Initialize add-to-wishlist script for cms pages and cart page. For category, search results and PDP this script is already initialized by Magento.
                        Handle the scenario where icon/image inside wishlist add-to trigger is missing.
                    </description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="1.0.2" date="2022-07-21">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove duplicated tag in changelog file</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="1.0.3" date="2022-08-30">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Expand wishlist feature to additional areas</overview>
                    <description>
                        Initialize add-to-wishlist script for all cms pages (not only homepage).
                        For category page, script was already initialized by Magento but only if product list was present.
                        In case when category page was used as a landing page with static block type content only it was not applied.
                        Now such scenario is also covered.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>SCAFA-683</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="1.0.4" date="2022-11-25">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add redirect to login page when ajax request is done for guest user</overview>
                    <description>
                        Adding product to wishlist is possible only for logged in users by default (without guest-wishlist module).
                        Ajax request not resolved with `backUrl` as a response will trigger redirect to login page with proper param
                        in order to add the product to the wishlist right after logging in.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>HAKA-1759</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="1.0.5" date="2022-12-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix for doubled products when I merge guest and logged in user's Wishlist</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4122</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
        </changelog>
    </module>
</config>
